(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
SHARK CITY
Loading...
hololive Presents
For One Night Only
Gawr Gura 3D Birthday Concert
ぐらの誕生日祝い
Gura's Birthday Celebration
I look up above the stars are bright
Yet I'm blinded by your light
Heaven seems so far away
Come back to me someday
The sky seems so blue
They lead me to you
Somewhere there's a place in my heart
In the skies above
(Screams)
SHINKIRO
照りつく日差し　ほどけた髪　帽子の先",
The scorching sun, loose hair, the tip of my hat
見覚えある　青いワゴン　止まるフラッシュバック
A familiar blue wagon, a stopping flashback
水際に駆けた　悪戯な魔法は
The mischievous magic that ran across the water's edge
遠い夏の　あの目まいに　戻さないで
Don't send me back to that dizziness of a distant summer
Baby love, stay my heart
なりふり構わず　Kissを奪って
Regardless of how it looks, steal a kiss from me
どこまでも
To the very end
今だけは寄り添ってあげるわ
Just for now, I'll stay close to you
唇にぬくもり残して
Leaving warmth upon my lips
肩すくめて　ボンネットから腰上げて
Shrugging my shoulders, I lift myself off the hood
喋りすぎよ　飽きてきたわ　ステップ踏み出したい
You talk too much, I'm getting bored.
I want to start stepping out.
見た瞳　瞳　誘いかけた魔法
Those eyes I saw, those eyes,
the magic that invited me in
ビビッドな夏の　あのめまいに戻りたいの
ビジュドゥロマン
I want to return to that vivid summer dizziness,
Bijou de roman
Baby Love　Stay My Heart　さりげない仕草して
Baby Love, stay in my heart,
with a casual gesture
Kissを　誘う　合図ね
It's a signal inviting a kiss, isn't it?
夕立につきあえないから
Because I can't keep up with the evening shower
偶然出会うオーシャンは　波のまにまに
The ocean we meet by chance
is at the mercy of the waves
Baby Love　Stay My Heart　何もかも蜃気楼
Baby Love, stay in my heart,
everything is a mirage
夏の　女神の　気まぐれね
It's the whim of the summer goddess, isn't it?
いつかまただなんて　I'll never say
Saying "someday again" is something I'll never say
唇にうらはらの　残したままで
Leaving the opposite on my lips as is
ANGEL
Lyrics: 古澤大 Music: 杉山洋介
Lyrics: Dai Furusawa Music: Yosuke Sugiyama
水辺　ついに　貝殻探して　ふと迷い
By the waterside, finally, searching for shells
and suddenly lost
明日ゆきの　フェリー間に合わず　途方に暮れる
Missing the ferry for tomorrow,
left at a complete loss
カセット青　もう夏の片隅
The blue cassette, already a corner of summer
砂の城は　過ぎたロマン
The sandcastle is a romance of the past
甘いささやき　心をえぐり　落ちるのが
Sweet whispers, gouging the heart,
if falling down...
嫌なら　雨に濡れたら　口紅を拭き　ただ思い出すの
...is what you hate, then if you get wet,
wipe your lipstick and just remember
ひめごとの　終わりに誰もが　一人で寝顔
At the end of a secret,
everyone has a sleeping face alone
空に寄る 潤むなら
If the sky leans, if it gets wet,
少し月は残して
leave a little bit of the moon.
時よなど 分からなくていい
It's okay not to know the time,
夜の底で 描いていたーい
I want to keep drawing at the bottom of the night.
君がもし かつてのように
If you find it impossible
笑うのが 無理なら
to laugh as you once did,
浅い眠りに 誘われたふり
pretend to be invited into a shallow sleep,
背中向けて 聞けばいい
and just turn your back and listen.
愛さないの ２人は
We won't love,
愛せないの
we can't love.
あの君はどこに
Where is that you?
夏のように 消える
Disappearing like summer.
時は過ぎ去り 夏はまた去り
Time passes, summer leaves again,
落ちてゆく 天使も
even the falling angels.
雨濡れたから 紅を拭き
Since I got wet in the rain, I wipe my lipstick,
ただ思い出しただけ
I just remembered.
Your call is smiley smiley
For my angel
This is my melody for you, yes please
Smile, angel
淋しい熱帯魚
Samishii Nettaigyo
STOP! 星屑で 髪を飾り
STOP! Adorning hair with stardust,
STOP! 優しい目を 待つわビーナス
STOP! Waiting for kind eyes, Venus.
Zuki-Zuki せつなく 震える胸
My chest throbs and trembles painfully.
まぼろしでもいい 会いたいのに
Even if it's an illusion, even though I want to see you.
Heart on wave
あなたは来ない
You won't come.
淋しい熱帯魚
Lonely Tropical Fish
あなたはこの愛
You are this love
私の思いを 拒絶しないで
Please don't reject my feelings
Lonely ユラユラ Swimming
Lonely, swaying, swimming
ユラユラ Dreaming
Swaying, dreaming
愛がゆれている
Love is wavering
Stop!
La 花柄の
La, with the floral patterns
水着だけが
Only my swimsuit
Love Me 目立ちすぎて
Love me, standing out too much
泣きたくなるの
I feel like crying
Shiny, Shiny こぎ手のない
Shiny, shiny, without a rower
その痛みを
That pain
冷めたい水辺に
In the cold water's edge
そっと浮かべて
Gently floating it
Heart Away
泳ぎだすけど
Starting to swim
あなたの夢には
But in your dreams
追いつけなくて
I can't catch up
I Can’t 出逢った日
I can't, the day we met
苦しいのに
Though it was painful
なぜ なぜ あなたじゃ
Why, why, if it's not you
なきゃダメなの
It just won't do
Lonely ユラユラ Swimming
Lonely, swaying, swimming
ユラユラ Dreaming
Swaying, dreaming
愛がゆれている
Love is wavering
Stop!
Heart Away
あなたはこの愛
You are this love
私の思いを
My feelings
拒絶しないで
Please don't reject
Heart Away
泳ぎだすけど
Starting to swim
あなたの夢には
But in your dreams
追いつけなくて
I can't catch up
テレフォン・ナンバー
Lyrics: 三浦徳子 Music: 佐藤健
Telephone Number
Lyrics: Yoshiko Miura Music: Takeshi Sato
Ah, 5-6-7-8-9
忘れないで
Please don't forget
私のテレフォン・ナンバー
My telephone number
困った時
When you're in trouble
ダイヤルしてほしい いつでも
I want you to dial it, anytime
So every night
飲みつづけている あなたの
Drinking up your
淋しさに ああ
Loneliness, ah
気づいていた ああ
I've noticed it, ah
Oh!
Ah, 5-6-7-8-9
背の高い
Tall...
あなたが小さく見えるから
Because you look so small
旅立つ朝 笑顔でいて欲しい
I want you to be smiling on the morning you depart
お願い
Please
So everyday
ベルを気にしては
Watching the phone
くるうわ
Going crazy
この愛に
To this love
気づいたら
If you notice it
Woah...
Loving me
Awoo!
5-6-7-0-9
Awoo! Awoo! Awoo!
Upside down, endless nights
Upside down, over the night
揺れる景色 心模様
Wavering scenery, state of mind
響く言葉 Afterwards
Echoing words, afterwards
漂う魅惑 世界を透かして
Floating charms, looking through the world
カウントダウン Yeah yeah
Countdown, yeah yeah
かたことの切り端と
Fragmented bits of words
語らう空からと
From the sky we talk to
Upside down, endless nights
今宵は眠らずに
Without sleeping tonight
Upside down, midnight
踊り明かそうよ
Let's dance the night away
Upside down, endless nights
リズムに乗っちゃえば
If you just get into the rhythm
Upside down, over the night
心も弾む
My heart also bounces
跳ねるヴィーナス 乙女心
Bouncing Venus, a girl's heart
辿る奇跡 Seventeen
The miracle I trace, seventeen
ためらう刺激 本能任せて
Hesitant stimulation, leaving it to instinct
YOUTHFUL DAYS' GRAFFITI
アウェイ！
Away!
沸き上がる本当の感情を
Surging with my true emotions...
漂う意識とかき混ぜて
...I mix them with my drifting consciousness.
Upside down take me tonight
夜空のステージで
On the night sky stage
Upside down me in the dark
踊り明かそうよ
Let's dance the night away
Upside down endless tonight
リズムに乗っちゃえば
If you get into the rhythm
Upside down all over the world
跳び出そうよ
Let's jump out
Upside down today's the night
夜空の向こうまで
To the other side of the night sky
Upside down morning sun
手を振ってみようよ
Let's try waving our hands
Upside down endless tonight
今日をもっと超えちゃえば
If we go even further beyond today
Upside down all over the world
明日はグッド・サンシャイン
Tomorrow will be good sunshine
Upside down take me tonight
今夜は眠れずに
Without being able to sleep tonight
Upside down me in the dark
踊り明かそうよ
Let's dance the night away
Upside down endless tonight
リズムに乗っちゃえば
If you get into the rhythm
Upside down all over the world
心も弾む
My heart bounces too
Upside down today's the night
夜空の向こうまで
To the other side of the night sky
Upside down morning sun
手を振ってみようよ
Let's try waving our hands
Upside down endless tonight
今日をもっと超えちゃえば
If we go even further beyond today
Upside down all over the world
明日はグッド・サンシャイン
Tomorrow will be good sunshine
Plastic Love
Lyrics ・ Music : 竹内まりや
Lyrics ・ Music : Mariya Takeuchi
突然のキスや
A sudden kiss or...
熱い眼差しで
...a passionate gaze.
恋のプログラムを
Don't let the program of love...
狂わせないでね
...get thrown into chaos.
出会いは別れ...
Encounters are partings...
呪文を急に打ち込んで
Suddenly casting a spell
時間が経てば終わる Don't worry
As time passes, it will end, don't worry
愛に傷ついたあの日からずっと
Ever since that day I was hurt by love
昼と夜が逆の暮らしを続けて
I've continued living with day and night reversed
流行りのディスコで踊り明かすうちに
While dancing the night away at a trendy disco
覚えた魔術なのよ I'm sorry
This is the magic I've learned, I'm sorry
私の事を決して本気で愛さないで
Please don't ever love me seriously
恋なんてただのゲーム 楽しめばそれでいいの
Love is just a game, it's fine as long as you enjoy it
閉ざした心飾る 派手なドレスも靴も
Even the flashy dresses and shoes that decorate my closed heart
孤独な友達
Are lonely friends
私を誘う人は皮肉なものね いつも
The people who invite me are ironic, aren't they, always
彼に似てるわ なぜか 思い出と重なり合う
For some reason, they look like him, overlapping with memories
グラスを落として急に 涙ぐんでも わけは
If I suddenly drop my glass and become teary-eyed
尋ねないでね
Please don't ask why
夜更けの高速で眠りにつく頃
Around the time I fall asleep on the late-night highway
ハロゲンライトだけ妖しく輝く
Only the halogen lights shine mysteriously
氷のように冷たい女だと
That I'm a woman as cold as ice
囁く声がしても Don't worry
Even if those whispering voices are heard, don't worry
I'm just playing games I know that's plastic love
Dance to the plastic beat another morning comes
SHYNESS BOY
Lyrics / Music : 角松敏生
Lyrics / Music : Toshiki Kadomatsu
夏のパーティで声を
At the summer party
かけてきたのはあなたの方からよ
You were the one who spoke to me first
いつも電話の声は
Your voice on the phone is always
ありきたりね
So ordinary
わかったことだけに言ってるの
I'm only talking about what I've understood.
You are my shyness boy 待ってるのよ
You are my shyness boy, I'm waiting.
さそいの言葉
Words of invitation.
もどかしさなら今日限りにしてほしい
I want the frustration to end today.
I'm fallin' love
夜のドライブのあとで
After the night drive.
遅いから送るよなんて
Saying "it's late, so I'll see you home".
あんまりね
It's just too much.
今日は朝までずっと
So that today, we can be
一緒にいられるように
together until morning,
してあるの
I've made sure of it.
You are my shyness boy 照れたいの
You are my shyness boy, I want to be shy.
あなたの愛は
Your love is...
タバコ持っててもふるえてるわダメなひと
trembling even while holding a cigarette, you hopeless person.
You are my shyness boy 待ってるのよ
You are my shyness boy, I'm waiting.
決まり文句を
For that cliché line.
やさしすぎるあなたの瞳
In those eyes of yours that are too kind,
そこが好き
that's what I like.
You are my shyness boy 待ってるのよ
You are my shyness boy, I'm waiting.
さそいの言葉
Words of invitation.
もどかしさなら今日限りにしてほしい
I want the frustration to end today.
You are my shyness boy 待ってるのよ
You are my shyness boy, I'm waiting.
決まり文句を
For that cliché line.
やさしすぎるあなたの瞳
In those eyes of yours that are too kind,
そこが好き
that's what I like.
未来派Lovers
Lyrics: 冬杜花代子 Music: 田中公平
Miraipa Lovers
Lyrics: Kayoko Fuyumori Music: Kohei Tanaka
キミにいかれてメタメタメカクシ
I'm crazy for you, completely blindfolded.
Heartbeatを合わせりゃそれで生きそうよ
If we match our heartbeats, I'll come alive.
キミとあたしは未来派好みのTechnician
You and I are technicians in the style of Futurism.
高く早く好きを気ままに
High and fast, liking as we please.
メタル・ボディの肌触りさえ
Even the touch of a metal body...
あつく感じてくるクセになりそう
feels hot, it might become a habit.
チャチなImagination超えた事件で
With an incident that exceeds cheap imagination,
重力違反あぬけるFeelingとめないで
don't stop the feeling of escaping gravity.
キミにいかれてメタメタメカクシ
I'm crazy for you, completely blindfolded.
Heart繋げばSpark上がるVoltage
If we connect our hearts, sparks fly and the voltage rises.
キミとあたしは未来派好みのTechnician
You and I are technicians in the style of Futurism.
つなぎっぱなし自由自在に
Staying connected, freely as we wish.
Nothing impossible
ぐるりとりまくエンジン・ツー世界
A world surrounded by Engine II.
軽く飛び越えてよあたしをつれて
Jump over it lightly and take me with you.
次のワープも
To the next warp too.
予測できない
Unpredictable,
100年早い
a hundred years too soon.
あー、恋人なの I'm in love with you
Ah, we're lovers, I'm in love with you.
君に射抜かれて
Shot through by you,
メタメタメチャメチャ
I'm falling deeply,
狂おしい
madly in love.
ハートビート合わせる
Match our heartbeats,
準備できて
get ready,
それでいきそうよ
that's how it's gonna go.
君と私は 未来派
You and I are futurists,
個性的 テクニシャン
unique technicians.
高く
Higher,
早く
faster,
好きよ
I love you,
気ままに
just as I please.
君に射抜かれて
Shot through by you,
メタメタメチャメチャ
I'm falling deeply,
狂おしい
madly in love.
ぴったり だからね
We're a perfect fit,
ピカイチ 切れる
top-tier and sharp,
アルポンス
Alponse.
君と私は 未来派
You and I are futurists,
個性的 テクニシャン
unique technicians.
空も
The sky,
海も
the sea,
今日も
today,
明日も
and tomorrow.
ナッシング・インポッシブル
Nothing impossible,
nothing impossible!
J-J-J-Domo birthday sharky desu!
D-D-D-Domo, it's the birthday shark!
Happy birthday to me!
Hi! How did you enjoy the live?
Hello, hello!
Ooh, birthday merch time! Ooh!
This birthday features beautiful art by the ultra-talented Utachako-tan!
This time inspired by the city pop genre.
I got the hot rod behind me, I'm in my 80s inspired idol outfit.
Get in, Ebies, we're going cruising!
This piece also will be available as a canvas.
You know what that means? Shark art appreciation time! Hehe!
Also by Utachako-san,
a really cool sweatshirt featuring these plans and coordinates to the ultimate shark girl. Hehe!
This design has so many little details.
I can't decide if I want to wear mine
or display it,
or- or buy one to wear and one to display.
Ah, I don't know!
But I love it so much, I think this is one of my favorite merch designs
I've ever come across for myself, so I'm really excited!
And then we have the Shark Keychain! You can match with me!
It's the same one I'm wearing in the canvas illustration.
There's a little Ebi, and a little Sharky,
and a trident, and it's blue,
my favorite color, and it's so cute!
If everyone matches together, we can spot-
spot each other in the wild
and then make awkward eye contact.
It'll be great, right?
And finally, if you purchase the set as a bundle,
it'll come with a very exclusive polaroid, hand-signed by me!
The bundle option is of course limited, so act quickly if you're interested.
The links to the- the purchasing of the merchandise
will be available in the description
and probably alongside the- the chat.
Hello! Hello in the chat bar! Yes, woohoo!
Okay, I'm off to eat a very large piece of cake that does not say "feet" on it.
Totally. Ha... Not this year. Maybe next year. Heh.
Thanks for coming to my birthday party! Yippee!
Buh-bye now! Thank you! Buh-bye!